Panama
Marist Archives and Special Collections
Panama
2.1.1.1.18
Marist College
MMM
MMM
MMM
  Box 1214
- Panama, 2.1.1.1.18
  - Along Colón waterfront, 1907; 1; 1000; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1214)
  - Lighthouse and bay at Colón, 1907; 2; 1001; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1214)
  - Frank R. Roberson in Monkey Hill Cemetery, near Colón, 1907; 3; 1002; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1214)
  - Frank R. Roberson in Monkey Hill Cemetery, near Colón, 1907; 4; 1003; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1214)
  - Railroad train at Colón Station, 1907; 5; 1004; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1214)
  - Bolivar Street, old houses, railroad tracks, Colón, 1907; 6; 1005; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1214)
  - Railroad Street, Colón, 1907; 7; 1006; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1214)
  - Episcopal church, Colón, 1907; 8; 1007; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1214)
  - Street in Colón, 1907; 9; 1008; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1214)
  - Hospital, nurse’s home and private quarters, Colón, 1907; 10; 1009; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1214)
  - I.C.C. Hospital, main entrance, Colón, 1907; 11; 1010; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1214)
  - Two native houses up near Mohey Hill[?], near Colón, 1907; 12; 1011; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1214)
  - Panama Railroad offices, Colón, 1907; 13; 1012; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1214)
  - Frank R. Roberson and American Consul at Colón, 1907; 14; 1013; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1214)
  - French and British Consuls in Colón, 1907; 15; 1014; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1214)
  - Along the sea front at Colón showing monument to builders of the Panama Railroad, 1907; 16; 1015; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1214)
  - Street along the coast at Colón, monument to builders of the Panama Railroad, 1907; 17; 1016; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1214)
  - Commissary and yards at Colón, 1907; 18; 1017; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1214)
  - American Consul at Colón, 1907; 19; 1018; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1214)
  - Billboards, Colón, 1907; 20; 1019; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1214)
  - Y.M.C.A. secretaries, Sliekal[?], Wolf, Purman[?] and Baxley, Cristobal, 1907; 21; 1020; 5; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1214)
  - Roosevelt Avenue, coconut trees, Cristobal (Larkin Co.), 1907; 22; 1021; 107; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1214)
  - Third Avenue, Y.M.C.A., Cristobal, 1907; 23; 1022; 27; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1214)
  - Public school at Cristobal, 1907; 24; 1023; 44; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1214)
  - Interior of Y.M.C.A., 1907; 25; 1024; 72; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1214)
  - Railroad Street in Cristobal, railroad station in background, 1907; 26; 1025; 47; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1214)
  - Interior of school at Cristobal, Frank R. Roberson in rear of classroom, 1907 October 28; 27; 1026; 43; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1214)
  - Government houses, Y.M.C.A., in Cristobal, 1907; 28; 1027; 30; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1214)
  - Union Church in Cristobal, Frank R. Roberson standing outside, 1907; 29; 1028; 45; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1214)
  - Interior of Union Church, man at altar, woman and child at organ, Cristobal, 1907; 30; 1029; 46; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1214)
  - Interior of schoolroom (Frank R. Roberson sent to Beseler Lantern Slide Company), 1907; 31; 1030; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1214)
  - Where the Atlantic and Chagres River meet (Frank R. Roberson sent to Beseler Lantern Slide Company), 1907; 32; 1031; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1214)
  - Boats on Chagres, village (Frank R. Roberson sent to Beseler Lantern Slide Company), 1907; 33; 1032; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1214)
  - Native women making butter, flat stone with flat powder, 1907; 34; 1033; 28; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1214)
  - Beach of Chagres village, 1907; 35; 1034; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1214)
  - Beach of Chagres village, 1907; 36; 1034A; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1214)
  Box 1215
- Panama, 2.1.1.1.18
  - The village street at Chagres (Frank R. Roberson sent to Beseler Lantern Slide Company), 1907; 1; 1035; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1215)
  - Approaching Chagres village (Frank R. Roberson sent to Beseler Lantern Slide Company), 1907; 2; 1036; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1215)
  - Village street of Chagres (Frank R. Roberson sent to Beseler Lantern Slide Company), 1907; 3; 1037; 48; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1215)
  - Frank R. Roberson and others at lunch, Chagres (Frank R. Roberson sent to Beseler Lantern Slide Company), 1907; 4; 1038; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1215)
  - Native street at Chagres (Frank R. Roberson sent to Beseler Lantern Slide Company), 1907; 5; 1039; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1215)
  - Belgian engines near the Chagres River (Frank R. Roberson sent to Beseler Lantern Slide Company), 1907; 6; 1040; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1215)
  - Line of old Belgian engines on the Chagres River (Frank R. Roberson sent to Beseler Lantern Slide Company), 1907; 7; 1041; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1215)
  - Chagres River from Fort Lorenzo (Frank R. Roberson sent to Beseler Lantern Slide Company), 1907; 8; 1042; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1215)
  - Frank R. Roberson and party at Fort Lorenzo (Frank R. Roberson sent to Beseler Lantern Slide Company), 1907; 9; 1043; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1215)
  - Old Spanish watch tower at Fort Lorenzo, two natives, Chagres, 1907; 10; 1044; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1215)
  - In Fort Lorenzo at Chagres [possibly Frank R. Roberson in foreground] (Frank R. Roberson sent to Beseler Lantern Slide Company), 1907; 11; 1046; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1215)
  - Interior of old Spanish fort at Chagres (Frank R. Roberson sent to Beseler Lantern Slide Company), 1907; 12; 1047; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1215)
  - Old fort at Chagres, native in foreground (Frank R. Roberson sent to Beseler Lantern Slide Company), 1907; 13; 1048; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1215)
  - Old Fort Lorenzo at Chagres, two natives (Frank R. Roberson sent to Beseler Lantern Slide Company), 1907; 14; 1049; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1215)
  - Gatún, site of the twin locks, points between buildings show entire width, 1907; 15; 1050; 33; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1215)
  - Gatún, showing beginning of the dam (Frank R. Roberson sent to Beseler Lantern Slide Company), 1907; 16; 1051; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1215)
  - Old native village at Gatún, where dam will be (Frank R. Roberson sent to Beseler Lantern Slide Company), 1907; 17; 1052; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1215)
  - Native houses, Gatún (Print to Larkin), 1907; 18; 1053; 108; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1215)
  - Old Belgian engines near Empire (Larkin Co.), 1907; 19; 1054; 110; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1215)
  - Gorgona shops (Frank R. Roberson sent to Beseler Lantern Slide Company), 1907; 20; 1055; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1215)
  - Gorgona shops (Frank R. Roberson sent to Beseler Lantern Slide Company, print to Larkin Co.), 1907; 21; 1056; 106; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1215)
  - From railroad station, Gorgona (Frank R. Roberson sent to Beseler Lantern Slide Company, print to Larkin Co.), 1907; 22; 1057; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1215)
  - Gorgona shops, 1907; 23; 1058; 26; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1215)
  - Gorgona shops, 1907; 24; 1059; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1215)
  - Outside dining room, Gorgona (Frank R. Roberson sent to Beseler Lantern Slide Company), 1907; 25; 1060; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1215)
  - Canal Zone Public School, Gorgona (Frank R. Roberson sent to Beseler Lantern Slide Company), 1907; 26; 1061; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1215)
  - Gorgona from the hill, 1907; 27; 1062; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1215)
  - Gorgona Railroad station, 1907; 28; 1063; 41; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1215)
  - Beautiful tree on the Chagres near Gorgona (Frank R. Roberson sent to Beseler Lantern Slide Company), 1907; 29; 1064; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1215)
  - Old French machinery near Gorgona (Frank R. Roberson sent to Beseler Lantern Slide Company), 1907; 30; 1065; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1215)
  - Discarded Belgian machinery near Gorgona (Frank R. Roberson sent to Beseler Lantern Slide Company), 1907; 31; 1066; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1215)
  - Interior of soldiers quarters, Camp Elliott, 1907; 32; 1067; 37; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1215)
  - General view of Culebra Cut, from Paraíso end, 1907; 33; 1068; 36; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1215)
  - Culebra Cut (Frank R. Roberson sent to Beseler Lantern Slide Company), 1907; 34; 1069; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1215)
  - Showing work in Big Cut (Obispo Cut), 1907; 35; 1070; 37; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1215)
  Box 1216
- Panama, 2.1.1.1.18
  - Culebra Cut from near Empire, 1907; 1; 1071; 46; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1216)
  - Dynamite explosion, workers running, Culebra, 1907; 2; 1072; 33; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1216)
  - Rock drills, Culebra, 1907; 3; 1073; 31; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1216)
  - Dirt train in the cut (Frank R. Roberson sent to Beseler Lantern Slide Company), 1907; 4; 1074; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1216)
  - Frank R. Roberson in mouth of steam shovel, 1907; 5; 1075; 35; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1216)
  - Steam shovel at work, man in mouth of shovel, Culebra, 1907; 6; 1076; 34; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1216)
  - Obispo Cut, 1907; 7; 1077; 29; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1216)
  - Culebra Cut (Frank R. Roberson sent to Beseler Lantern Slide Company), 1907; 8; 1078; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1216)
  - Overall view of Culebra Cut, 1907; 9; 1079; 30; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1216)
  - Obispo Cut, box of dynamite in foreground, 1907; 10; 1080; 30; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1216)
  - Showing work in Bas Obispo Cut, workers with drills, railroad tracks, 1907; 11; 1081; 39; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1216)
  - Town of Culebra, 1907; 12; 1082; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1216)
  - Steam shovel at work in Culebra Cut near Empire, looking toward Obispo (Sold to Larkin Co. by Roy E. Hallock, copyright 1908 by the Roberson Travel Lectures), 1907; 13; 1083; 109; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1216)
  - Steam drills at work, preparing for dynamite, Frank R. Roberson in foreground (Sold to Larkin Co. by Roy E. Hallock, copyright 1908 by the Roberson Travel Lectures), 1907; 14; 1084; 112; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1216)
  - Culebra Cut from Gold Hill (Frank R. Roberson sent to Beseler Lantern Slide Company, print sent to Larkin Co.), 1907; 15; 1085; 100; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1216)
  - Culebra Cut, looking toward the Pacific (Frank R. Roberson sent to Beseler Lantern Slide Company, print sent to Larkin Co.), 1907; 16; 1086; 102; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1216)
  - Culebra Cut, showing different levels on terraces (Frank R. Roberson sent to Beseler Lantern Slide Company, print to Larkin Co.), 1907; 17; 1087; 103; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1216)
  - Culebra Cut (Frank R. Roberson sent to Beseler Lantern Slide Company, print to Larkin Co.), 1907; 18; 1088; 101; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1216)
  - Work in Culebra Cut, showing different levels in work (Frank R. Roberson sent to Beseler Lantern Slide Company, print to Larkin Co. billed to Roy E. Hallock, Larkin Co. copyright 1908 by the Roberson Travel Lectures), 1907; 19; 1089; 104; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1216)
  - Bas Obispo Cut (Larkin Co.), 1907; 20; 1090; 113; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1216)
  - Showing homes in Culebra (Frank R. Roberson sent to Beseler Lantern Slide Company, sold to Larkin Co. by Roy E. Hallock, copyright 1908 by the Roberson Travel Lectures), 1907; 21; 1091; 105; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1216)
  - Interior of Commissary mess hall where men eat, Empire, 1907; 22; 1092; 38; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1216)
  - Vault of U.S. Bank at Empire (Frank R. Roberson sent to Beseler Lantern Slide Company), 1907; 23; 1093; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1216)
  - Houses at Empire (Frank R. Roberson sent to Beseler Lantern Slide Company), 1907; 24; 1094; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1216)
  - Empire street scene (Larkin Co.), 1907; 25; 1095; 111; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1216)
  - Old Belgian engines at Empire, 1907; 26; 1096; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1216)
  - Engine overgrown with vines, Empire, 1907; 27; 1097; 42; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1216)
  - Frank R. Roberson and Mrs. Jessie W. Roberson on porch of the Hotel Tivoli, Ancón, 1907; 28; 1098; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1216)
  - View from the Hotel Tivoli balcony, Frank R. Roberson and Mrs. Jessie W. Roberson on chairs, Ancón, 1907; 29; 1099; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1216)
  - Looking from the Hotel Tivoli at Ancón toward the Bay of Panama, 1907; 30; 1100; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1216)
  - Rear of Hotel Tivoli at Ancón (Frank R. Roberson sent to Beseler Lantern Slide Company), 1907; 31; 1101; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1216)
  - Road up Ancón Hill, where officers live (Frank R. Roberson sent to Beseler Lantern Slide Company), 1907; 32; 1103; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1216)
  Box 1217
- Panama, 2.1.1.1.18
  - In Old Panama, 1907; 1; 1155; 4x5 (Box 1217)
  - In the Panama Prison, 1907; 2; 1156; 4x5 (Box 1217)
  - Loving couple, 1907; 3; 1159; 4x5 (Box 1217)
  - Old Panama market, 1907; 4; 1162; 4x5 (Box 1217)
  - Prisoners fighting in Panama, 1907; 5; 1164; 4x5 (Box 1217)
  - Baseball in Panama, 1907; 6; 1166; 4x5 (Box 1217)
  - Prisoners washing clothes, 1907; 7; 1167; 4x5 (Box 1217)
  - Native woman washing, 1907; 8; 1169; 4x5 (Box 1217)
  - Fire engine house, Ancón, 1907; 9; 1176; 4x5 (Box 1217)
  - Native life, 1907; 10; 1179; 4x5 (Box 1217)
  - Small restaurant along railroad, 1907; 11; 1186; 4x5 (Box 1217)
  - Along railroad from rear of train, 1907; 12; 1187; 4x5 (Box 1217)
  - Along the railroad from rear of train, 1907; 13; 1188; 4x5 (Box 1217)
  - Along railroad from rear of train, 1907; 14; 1189; 4x5 (Box 1217)
  - Along the railroad track, 1907; 15; 1194; 4x5 (Box 1217)
  - Public school, 1907; 16; 1195; 4x5 (Box 1217)
  - School house, 1907; 17; 1196; 4x5 (Box 1217)
  - Man at the pay car, 1907; 18; 1197; 4x5 (Box 1217)
  - Chagres River, 1907; 19; 1198; 4x5 (Box 1217)
  - Hotel manager at Ancón, 1907; 20; 1199; 4x5 (Box 1217)
  - Steam shovel, La Boca, 1907; 21; 1200; 4x5 (Box 1217)
  - Waiting to be paid at La Boca, 1907; 22; 1201; 4x5 (Box 1217)
  - La Boca, 1907; 23; 1202; 4x5 (Box 1217)
  - La Boca docks, 1907; 24; 1203; 4x5 (Box 1217)
  - Dredging entrance to canal, La Boca, 1907; 25; 1204; 4x5 (Box 1217)
  - Tobago Island in distance?, 1907; 26; 1205; 4x5 (Box 1217)
  - Men being paid, La Boca, 1907; 27; 1206; 4x5 (Box 1217)
  - Milk vendors, La Boca, 1907; 28; 1207; 4x5 (Box 1217)
  - Crowd of workmen at La Boca, 1907; 29; 1208; 4x5 (Box 1217)
  - Engine at La Boca, 1907; 30; 1209; 4x5 (Box 1217)
  - South American steamer at La Boca docks, 1907; 31; 1210; 4x5 (Box 1217)
  - Men at work at La Boca, 1907; 32; 1211; 4x5 (Box 1217)
  - Loading a car at La Boca wharf, 1907; 33; 1212; 4x5 (Box 1217)
  - Steam shovel at work, 1907; 34; 1213; 4x5 (Box 1217)
  - Steam shovels, 1907; 35; 1214; 4x5 (Box 1217)
  - Steam shovel at work, 1907; 36; 1215; 4x5 (Box 1217)
  - Culebra, steam shovel at work, 1907; 37; 1216; 4x5 film (Box 1217)
  - Culebra, steam shovel at work, 1907; 38; 1216A; 4x5 film (Box 1217)
  - Culebra, steam shovel, 1907; 39; 1216B; 4x5 film (Box 1217)
  - Culebra, steam shovel in distance, 1907; 40; 1216C; 4x5 film (Box 1217)
  - Steam shovel at work, 1907; 41; 1217; 4x5 (Box 1217)
  - Steam shovel, 1907; 42; 1218; 4x5 (Box 1217)
  - Frank R. Roberson on steam shovel, 1907; 43; 1219; 4x5 (Box 1217)
  - Rear view of steam shovel, 1907; 44; 1220; 4x5 (Box 1217)
  - Culebra Cut and vicinity, steam shovels, Frank R. Roberson, 1907; 45; 1221; 4x5 (Box 1217)
  - Steam shovel at work, 1907; 46; 1222; 4x5 (Box 1217)
  - Steam shovel at work, 1907; 47; 1223; 4x5 (Box 1217)
  - Steam shovel at work, 1907; 48; 1224; 4x5 (Box 1217)
  - Shovels in Culebra, 1907; 49; 1225; 4x5 (Box 1217)
  - Culebra Cut, 1907; 50; 1233; 4x5 (Box 1217)
  - Culebra Cut, 1907; 51; 1234; 4x5 (Box 1217)
  - Steam shovel at work, 1907; 52; 1235; 4x5 (Box 1217)
  - Electric drill men, 1907; 53; 1236; 4x5 (Box 1217)
  - Drill men at work, 1907; 54; 1237; 4x5 (Box 1217)
  - Drill men at work, 1907; 55; 1239; 4x5 (Box 1217)
  - Gorgona and shops, 1907; 56; 1242; 4x5 (Box 1217)
  - Workmen coming from shops at Gorgona, 1907; 57; 1243; 4x5 (Box 1217)
  - Workmen coming from shops at Gorgona, 1907; 58; 1244; 4x5 (Box 1217)
  Box 1218
- Panama, 2.1.1.1.18
  - Gorgona shops, 1907; 1; 1245; 4x5 (Box 1218)
  - Shops at Gorgona, 1907; 2; 1246; 4x5 (Box 1218)
  - Men coming from Gorgona shop, 1907; 3; 1247; 4x5 (Box 1218)
  - In yards of shops at Gorgona, 1907; 4; 1248; 4x5 (Box 1218)
  - Men coming from shops at Gorgona, 1907; 5; 1249; 4x5 (Box 1218)
  - Bas Obispo and Empire, 1907 October 26; 6; 1250; 4x5 (Box 1218)
  - Bas Obispo Cut, 1907; 7; 1252; 4x5 (Box 1218)
  - Changed Colón[?], 1907; 8; 1266; 4x5 (Box 1218)
  - Statue of Columbus, Colón, Copy, before 1916; 9; 4x5 (Box 1218)
  - Panama Public School at Cristobal, 1907; 10; 1273; 4x5 (Box 1218)
  - Landing at Cristobal, 1907; 11; 1274; 4x5 (Box 1218)
  - Black children, 1907; 12; 1275; 4x5 (Box 1218)
  - Black babies, naked, 1907; 13; 1276; 4x5 (Box 1218)
  - Native black children, 1907; 14; 1277; 4x5 (Box 1218)
  - Made[?] from end of train near Black Swamp, 1907; 15; 1282; 4x5 (Box 1218)
  - School mistress and her children at Chagres, 1907; 16; 1284; 4x5 (Box 1218)
  - On the Chagres River, 1907; 17; 1285; 4x5 (Box 1218)
  - On the Chagres River, 1907; 18; 1286; 4x5 film (Box 1218)
  - On the Chagres River, 1907; 19; 1287; 4x5 (Box 1218)
  - Party on the Chagres, 1907; 20; 1289; 4x5 (Box 1218)
  - On the Chagres in the rain, Frank R. Roberson holding umbrella, 1907; 21; 1290; 4x5 (Box 1218)
  - On the Chagres river, Cayuga[?] under trees, 1907; 22; 1291; 4x5 (Box 1218)
  - Negro house on the Chagres, 1907; 23; 1292; 4x5 film (Box 1218)
  - Civil engineers, 1907; 24; 1293; 4x5 (Box 1218)
  - House on the Chagres, 1907; 25; 1294; 4x5 (Box 1218)
  - Native hut on the Chagres, 1907; 26; 1295; 4x5 (Box 1218)
  - Native house on the Chagres, 1907; 27; 1298; 4x5 (Box 1218)
  - Native house on the Chagres, 1907; 28; 1299; 4x5 (Box 1218)
  - House in Chagres village, 1907; 29; 1301; 4x5 (Box 1218)
  - Cayuga[?] on the Chagres, 1907; 30; 1304; 4x5 (Box 1218)
  - Panama Railroad, steamship line, 1907; 31; 1306; 4x5 (Box 1218)
  - Panama Railroad steamship line, 1907; 32; 1307; 4x5 (Box 1218)
  - Leaving New York for Panama, 1907; 33; 1308; 4x5 (Box 1218)
  - Going down North River, 1907; 34; 1309; 4x5 (Box 1218)
  - Lusitania at docks in North River, 1907; 35; 1310; 4x5 (Box 1218)
  - Lower New York from North River, 1907; 36; 1311; 4x5 (Box 1218)
  - Leaving the docks at New York, 1907; 37; 1312; 4x5 (Box 1218)
  - Leaving New York harbor, 1907; 38; 1313; 4x5 (Box 1218)
  - Lusitania at pier in North River, 1907; 39; 1314; 4x5 (Box 1218)
  - Lower New York from North River, 1907; 40; 1315; 4x5 (Box 1218)
  - Frank R. Roberson and Mrs. Jessie W. Roberson on the way to Panama, 1907; 41; 1316; 4x5 film (Box 1218)
  - Frank R. Roberson and Mrs. Jessie W. Roberson on the way to Panama, 1907; 42; 1316A; 4x5 film (Box 1218)
  - Captain Corning of the Panama, 1907; 43; 1317; 4x5 (Box 1218)
  - Snapshot of Mr. Gronow made on the Panama, 1908; 44; 2.5x3.5 film (Box 1218)
  - Captain of the Panama, before 1916; 45; 4x5 film (Box 1218)
  - Frank R. Roberson asleep on deck of ship, before 1916; 46; 4x5 (Box 1218)
  - Sunset at sea, 1907; 47; 1318; 4x5 (Box 1218)
  - Sunset at sea, 1907; 48; 1319; 4x5 (Box 1218)
  - Sunsets and sunrises, 1907; 49; 1320; 4x5 film (Box 1218)
  - Sunsets and sunrises, 1907; 50; 1320A; 4x5 film (Box 1218)
  - Sunsets and sunrises, 1907; 51; 1320B; 4x5 film (Box 1218)
  - Sunsets and sunrises, ship, 1907; 52; 1320C; 4x5 film (Box 1218)
  - Sunsets and sunrises, ship, 1907; 53; 1320D; 4x5 film (Box 1218)
  - Sunset, 1907; 54; 1322; 4x5 (Box 1218)
  - Sea scene, ship, 1907; 55; 1323; 4x5 film (Box 1218)
  - Sea scene, land in distance, 1907; 56; 1323A; 4x5 film (Box 1218)
  - Sea scene, sailboat in distance, 1907; 57; 1323B; 4x5 film (Box 1218)
  - Sea scene, land in distance, 1907; 58; 1323C; 4x5 film (Box 1218)
  - Sea scene, ship, 1907; 59; 1323D; 4x5 film (Box 1218)
  - Sea scene, ship, 1907; 60; 1323E; 4x5 film (Box 1218)
  - Sea scene, boat, close-up, 1907; 61; 1323F; 4x5 film (Box 1218)
  - Boat life, woman holding baby, 1907; 62; 1323G; 4x5 film (Box 1218)
  - Boat life, man on deck chair, reading, 1907; 63; 1323H; 4x5 film (Box 1218)
  - Boat life, man holding rope, 1907; 64; 1323I; 4x5 film (Box 1218)
  - Sunset, 1907; 65; 1324; 4x5 film (Box 1218)
  - Deck scene, 1907; 66; 1325; 4x5 (Box 1218)
  - On deck, going down, 1907; 67; 1326; 4x5 (Box 1218)
  - Funnel on “Panama”, 1907; 68; 1327; 4x5 (Box 1218)
  - Captain Corning of the Panama, 1907; 69; 1328; 4x5 (Box 1218)
  - Boat passing on way to Panama, 1907; 70; 1329; 4x5 (Box 1218)
  - Arrival at New York on return, small boats, 1907; 71; 1330; 4x5 film (Box 1218)
  - Arrival at New York on return, Statue of Liberty, 1907; 72; 1330A; 4x5 film (Box 1218)
  - Arrival at New York on return, city in distance, 1907; 73; 1330B; 4x5 film (Box 1218)
  - Sunset on board return trip, 1907 October 30; 74; 1331; 4x5 film (Box 1218)
  - Dynamite exploding (photograph by Fishbaugh Empire O.Z.), 1907; 75; 1332; 5x7 (Box 1218)
  - Dynamite charge being put off in Cut, 1907; 76; 1333; 5x7 (Box 1218)
  - Old dredge in Chagres River (photograph by Fishbaugh Empire O.Z.), 1907; 77; 1334; 5x7 (Box 1218)
  - Natives being paid, 1907; 78; 1335; 5x7 (Box 1218)
  - Large building, 1907; 79; 1336; 5x7 (Box 1218)
  - Drilling, 1907; 80; 1337; 5x7 (Box 1218)
  Box 1219
- Panama, 2.1.1.1.18
  - Narrow street in Panama (photograph by Fishbaugh Empire O.Z.), 1907; 1; 1338; 5x7 (Box 1219)
  - Ruins of Old Panama (photograph by Fishbaugh Empire O.Z.), 1907; 2; 1339; 5x7 (Box 1219)
  - Laborer’s quarters (by W.A. Fishbaugh), 1907; 3; 1340; 5x7 (Box 1219)
  - Panama lottery drawing (photograph by Fishbaugh Empire O.Z.), 1907; 4; 1341; 5x7 (Box 1219)
  - Skeleton in broken coffin, 1907; 5; 1342; 5x7 (Box 1219)
  - General view, Panama, 1907; 6; 1343; 5x7 (Box 1219)
  - Hospital ward, 1907; 7; 1344; 5x7 (Box 1219)
  - Native village, 1907; 8; 1345; 5x7 (Box 1219)
  - Seal of the Panama Canal, 1907; 9; 1346; 5x7 (Box 1219)
  - Men digging at Culebra Cut, before 1916; 10; 4x5 film (Box 1219)
  - Small boat on river, before 1916; 11; 4x5 film (Box 1219)
  - Woman holding baby, before 1916; 12; 4x5 film (Box 1219)
  - Woman washing clothes, before 1916; 13; 4x5 film (Box 1219)
  - Woman and two children on small boat, before 1916; 14; 4x5 film (Box 1219)
  - Woman and child, before 1916; 15; 4x5 film (Box 1219)
  - Woman holding baby, before 1916; 16; 4x5 film (Box 1219)
  - Woman washing laundry, before 1916; 17; 4x5 film (Box 1219)
  - Woman doing laundry, before 1916; 18; 4x5 film (Box 1219)
  - Workers at the Culebra Cut, before 1916; 19; 4x5 film (Box 1219)
  - Men working at the Cut, before 1916; 20; 4x5 film (Box 1219)
  - Cranes at the Cut, before 1916; 21; 4x5 film (Box 1219)
  - Black Swamp, 22; 4x5 (Box 1219)
  - South America, 23; 4x5 (Box 1219)
  - Ship canals of the world (copy), 1907; 24; 4x5 (Box 1219)
  - Facts concerning the Panama Canal (copy), 1907; 25; 4x5 (Box 1219)
  - Comparative distances and trade economics (copy), 1907; 26; 4x5 (Box 1219)
  - Canals of the United States (copy), 1907; 27; 4x5 (Box 1219)
  - Towing locomotives (copy), before 1914; 28; 200X; 4x5 (Box 1219)
  - Old man with pipe (copy), before 1914; 29; 201X; 4x5 (Box 1219)
  - Old woman (copy), before 1914; 30; 202X; 4x5 (Box 1219)
  - Drawings of lock mechanics (copy), before 1914; 31; 203X; 4x5 (Box 1219)
  - Panama Canal lock (copy), 1912 December; 32; 5x7 (Box 1219)
  - Aristides Agramonte (copy), before 1916; 33; 4x5 (Box 1219)
  - James Carroll (copy), before 1916; 34; 4x5 (Box 1219)
  - Mosquito diagrams (copy), before 1916; 35; 5x7 (Box 1219)
  Box 1220
- Panama, 2.1.1.1.18
  - Panorama of the Bay of Panama and Pacific entrance of the canal, 1908; 1; 8 x 10 (Box 1220)
  - Frank R. Roberson and American flag on board the United Fruit Company Steamer S.S. Carrillo, 1912 September 5-6; 2; 1348; 35; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1220)
  - Officers of the S.S. Carrillo, United Fruit Company Steamer, at sea, 1912 September 5-6; 3; 1349; 147; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1220)
  - Officers, United Fruit Company Steamer S.S. Carrillo, 1912 September 5-6; 4; 1350; 148; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1220)
  - Library and card room, United Fruit Company Steamer S.S. Carrillo, at sea, 1912 September 5-6; 5; 1351; 149; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1220)
  - On shipboard using sextant, United Fruit Company Steamer S.S. Carrillo, 1912 September 5-6; 6; 1352; 150; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1220)
  - Suite of rooms, United Fruit Company Steamer S.S. Carrillo, Frank R. Roberson reading book, 1912 September 5-6; 7; 1353; 151; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1220)
  - Captain Smith, United Fruit Company Steamer S.S. Carrillo, 1912 September 5-6; 8; 1354; 152; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1220)
  - Café, United Fruit Company Steamer S.S. Carrillo, 1912 September 5-6; 9; 1355; 153; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1220)
  - Dining room, United Fruit Company Steamer S.S. Carrillo, 1912 September 5-6; 10; 1356; 154; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1220)
  - Submarine telephone, United Fruit Company Steamer S.S. Carrillo, 1912 September 5-6; 11; 1357; 155; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1220)
  - Stairway, United Fruit Company Steamer S.S. Carrillo, 1912 September 5-6; 12; 1358; 157; 6.5x8.5 (Box 1220)